A Guide to the R. Bolling Batte Papers, 1918-1992
Library of Virginia
- Epes/Eppes Files (Box 42-45)
  - Eppes - Bradley Notes (Box 43, Folder 11)
  - Eppes - Brunswick (Box 43, Folder 12)
  - Epes of Brunswick - Compiled by Charles Hughes Hamlin (Box 43, Folder 13)
  - Eppes Family - Buckingham County Records (Box 43, Folder 14)
  - Eppes - Charles City County Records (Box 43, Folder 15)
  - Epes Chart - Make-ups for New Sheets (Box 43, Folder 16)
  - Epes Chart Material From Others (Box 43, Folder 17)
  - Eppes Chart Modifications (Box 43, Folder 18)
  - Epes Chart Work Completed (Box 43, Folder 19)
  - Eppes - Chesterfield (Box 43, Folder 20)
  - Eppes Family - Chesterfield County Records (Box 43, Folder 21)
  - Eppes Clippings (Box 43, Folder 22)
  - Epes - Clippings From Mrs. Turner (Box 43, Folder 23)
  - Eppes, Daniel Spain - Dinwiddie County (Box 43, Folder 24)
  - Eppes in Dinwiddie (Box 43, Folder 25)
  - Eppes - Dinwiddie - Land Tax (Box 43, Folder 26)
  - Eppes Family - Greensville County Records (Box 43, Folder 27)
  - Epes Family - Nottoway County Records (Box 43, Folder 28)
  - Nottoway Order Books 7-8-9 (Box 43, Folder 29)
  - Epes Family of Prince George (Box 43, Folder 30)
  - Eppes - Hamlin Notes (Box 43, Folder 31)
  - Epes - Hamlin Reports (First Copy) (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Epes - Hamlin Reports - 2nd Copy (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Eppes - Henrico (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Eppes Island Survey (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Epes, Julia Bagley - Pedigree Form (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Epes of Kent (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - Epes/Eppes - Land Tax Records (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - Epes Land Tax - Charles City (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - Epes - Land Tax - Nottoway and Amelia (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Epes, Lucy Ann - Legislative Petition and HD Journal Notes Concerning (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Eppes Marriages (Box 44, Folder 11)
  - Epes Marriages in Kent Through 1660 (Box 44, Folder 12)
  - Epes Material (Box 44, Folder 13)
  - Epes/Eppes Material For Family History (Box 44, Folder 14)
  - Epes Material From Mrs. Campbell Epes (Box 44, Folder 15)
  - Epes Material Received From Helen Holden (Box 44, Folder 16)
  - Eppes Material From Peebles to be Retained (Box 44, Folder 17)
  - Eppes Material - Worked Over - To Keep (Box 44, Folder 18)
  - Eppes - Misc. Data (Box 44, Folder 19)
  - Eppes - Notes From Mrs. Cutchin (Box 44, Folder 20)
  - Epes - Notes From Mrs. Kelly (Box 44, Folder 21)
  - Notes by Prentiss Price on Eppes (Box 44, Folder 22)
  - Eppes Notes by Prentiss Price (Box 44, Folder 23)
  - Eppes Papers to be Sorted (Box 44, Folder 24)
  - Eppes - Patents (Box 44, Folder 25)
  - Eppes - Petersburg (Box 44, Folder 26)
  - Epes - Photographs (Box 44, Folder 27)
  - Eppes Photostats - Deeds, Wills, etc. (Box 44, Folder 28)
  - Epes Photostats (Negatives) (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Epes - Prince George Great Book, 1713-1728 - Index (Peebles) (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Eppes - Prince George Records (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Epes Project Ground Rules (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Eppes - RBB File (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Eppes Related Families (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Eppes - Richmond (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Eppes Society (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - Eppes Surveys (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - Eppes, Thomas (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - Eppes in Virkus (Box 45, Folder 11)
  - FFFE Project (Box 45, Folder 12)
  - FFFF Project (Box 45, Folder 13)
  - FFFM Project (Box 45, Folder 14)
  - FFFS Project (Box 45, Folder 15)
  - FFLL Project (Box 45, Folder 16)
  - FFMF Project (Box 45, Folder 17)
  - FFMJ Project - Old Sheets Completed (Box 45, Folder 18)
  - FFMJ Project - Papers to Work From (Box 45, Folder 19)
  - FFWF Project (Box 45, Folder 20)
  - Francis Eppes (Box 45, Folder 21)
  - Francis Epes of Causons vs. George Lewis (Box 45, Folder 22)
  - Papers of Jarrett Epps (Box 45, Folder 23)
  - Photocopies From Epes Material in Alderman Library (Box 45, Folder 24)
  - Records Pertaining to Unidentified Epes/Eppes (Box 45, Folder 25)
  - Revisions to Epes Charts (by RBB) (Box 45, Folder 26)
  - Swem's Index to Eppes (Box 45, Folder 27)
  - 3V and 7V on Eppes (Box 45, Folder 28)
  - Trial Chart Revisions - Cases Not Thought Worth Expanding Beyond Eighth Generation (Box 45, Folder 29)
  - Trial Chart Revisions - Completed Cases (Box 45, Folder 30)
  - Trial Chart Revisions - Pending Cases (Box 45, Folder 31)
  - Unfinished Epes Society Work to be Done (Box 45, Folder 32)
- Jones Files (Box 46-48)
  The Jones files contain information compiled by Augusta B. Fothergill in the course of researching her book Peter Jones and Richard Jones Genealogies, published in 1924. They include court record abstracts, Bible records, correspondence, notes from other individuals and manuscript drafts.
  - Jones (Box 46, Folder 1-2)
  - Jones (Adam) (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Jones, Emory E. of West Virginia (Sussex-Bedford Jones) (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - John Jones of Brunswick (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - Jones, Lewellyn (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - "Ragsdale" Jones Line (J-9) (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - Robert R. Jones (Mordecai Jones Line) (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - Jones, Rowland and Orlando (Box 46, Folder 9)
  - Jones, W.R. re: Cadwallader Jones (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - Wood Jones (Box 46, Folder 11)
  - Jones - Amelia Records (Box 46, Folder 12)
  - Jones - Bedford Records (Box 46, Folder 13)
  - Jones - Blandford Records (Box 46, Folder 14)
  - Jones - Brunswick Records (Box 46, Folder 15)
  - Jones - Buckingham Records (Box 46, Folder 16)
  - Jones - Campbell Records (Box 46, Folder 17)
  - Jones - Charlotte Records (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Jones - Chesterfield Records (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Jones - Cumberland Records (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - Jones - Dinwiddie County Records (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - Jones - Halifax County Records (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - Jones Records in Henrico and Chesterfield (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - Jones Records in Isle of Wight (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - Jones Records in Lunenburg (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - Jones - Mecklenburg Records (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - Jones of Middlesex, Gloucester, and Hanover (Box 47, Folder 10)
  - Jones - Nottoway Records (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - Jones - Powhatan Records (Box 47, Folder 12)
  - Jones Records in Prince Edward (Box 47, Folder 13)
  - Jones Records in Prince George and Charles City (Box 47, Folder 14)
  - Jones - Southampton County (Box 47, Folder 15)
  - Jones - Record Extracts - Southampton (Box 47, Folder 16)
  - Jones - Surry (Box 47, Folder 17)
  - Jones - Surry Records Extracts (Box 47, Folder 18)
  - Jones - Sussex County Records (Box 47, Folder 19)
  - The Jones Families of Wales and Pennsylvania (Box 47, Folder 20)
  - Bible Records (Box 47, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence - Cole, Alyce Jones (Box 47, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence (Mary C. Hood, Isla Ragsdale, Sallie H.F. Jones) (Box 47, Folder 23)
  - Correspondence - Jones, Robert Randolph (Box 47, Folder 24)
  - Land Patents (Box 47, Folder 25)
  - Misc. Correspondence and Lines (Box 47, Folder 26)
  - Miscellaneous Items (Box 47, Folder 27)
  - Misc. Material to be Posted (Box 47, Folder 28)
  - Records from Counties North of James River (Except Henrico) (Box 47, Folder 29)
  - Out of State (Box 47, Folder 30)
  - Jones of Sussex and Brunswick - Mrs. Barber's Papers (Box 47, Folder 31)
  - W.H. Kilpatrick's Notes (Box 47, Folder 32)
  - Thixton Correspondence (Box 47, Folder 33)
  - Mrs. Harris E. Willingham (133) (Box 47, Folder 34)
  - Misc. Correspondence (Box 47, Folder 35)
  - Jones Book - Manuscript Material (Fothergill) (Box 48, Folder 1-3)
  - Misc. Notes (Fothergill Papers) (Box 48, Folder 4-5)
  - Jones - 132 (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - Jones - 132, 133, 134 (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Jones (133) (Box 48, Folder 8)
  - Jones - Correspondence (133) (Box 48, Folder 9)
  - Jones - 133 Documents (Box 48, Folder 10)
  - Jones - 134 (Front) (Box 48, Folder 11)
  - Jones - 134 (Box 48, Folder 12)
  - Jones - 147 (Box 48, Folder 13)
  - Jones - 147 Correspondence (Box 48, Folder 14)
- Card Files (Box 49-99)
  The biographical card files contain more than thirty thousand cards, each representing an individual. Each card gives as much information on the subject as was known when they were compiled, including date and place of birth, full names of parents, date and place of marriage(s), name of spouse, notation of education, public offices held, profession, military service, date and place of death, and place of burial. Codes are used on the right end of each line to indicate sources. On the backs of the cards appear extracts from pertinent documents, tombstone inscriptions, obituary notices and a listing of the subject's children.
  There is also an extensive alphabetical subject index to the Virginia Cavalcade. At the end of the card files is an index to the sources which were used in the compilation of the biographical card files. The canary yellow cards give the author of the source and are filed alphabetically. The cherry cards give the subject of the source and are also filed alphabetically. Also included are miscellaneous index cards to sources, counties, cities, family Bibles, cemetery records, census lists, marriage records, newspapers, other published sources, parish registers and wills which were used in the compilation of the card files. Finally, there is a title/subject card index covering articles appearing in Civil War Times Illustrated. All of the card files are available on microfilm (Misc. Reels 1952-2029).
  - A - Archer (Box 49)
  - Armat - Baker (Box 50)
  - Baldwin - Batts (Box 51)
  - Baugh - Blake (Box 52)
  - Blanchard - Botts (Box 53)
  - Bouldin - Brodie (Box 54)
  - Brodnax - Burwell (Box 55)
  - Bush - Carter (Box 56)
  - Cary - Claggett (Box 57)
  - Claiborne - Cockrill (Box 58)
  - Codd - Crozet (Box 59)
  - Crump - Dorrington (Box 60)
  - Doswell - Ellis (Box 61)
  - Ellyson - Flippen (Box 62)
  - Flood - Gaskins (Box 63)
  - Gates - Gray (Box 64)
  - Grayson - Hardaway (Box 65)
  - Hardee - Hatch (Box 66)
  - Hatcher - Holman (Box 67)
  - Holmes - Johnson (Box 68)
  - Johnston - Ledbetter (Box 69)
  - Lee - Lowry (Box 70)
  - Loyall - Maitland (Box 71)
  - Mallory - Mason (Box 72)
  - Massenburg - Minetree (Box 73)
  - Minge - Myhill (Box 74)
  - N - Owen (Box 75)
  - Pace - Pender (Box 76)
  - Pendleton - Poythress (Box 77)
  - Pratt - Regester (Box 78)
  - Reid - Rucker (Box 79)
  - Ruffin - Shipman (Box 80)
  - Shippen - Stalling (Box 81)
  - Stanard - Syme (Box 82)
  - T- Thomson (Box 83)
  - Thornburn - Tune (Box 84)
  - Tunstall - Walters (Box 85)
  - Walthall - Whitfield (Box 86)
  - Whiting - Wilmer (Box 87)
  - Wilson - Z (Box 88)
  - Epes/Eppes (Box 89)
  - Jones #1 (Box 90)
  - Jones # 2 (Box 91)
  - Subjects A - Bl (Box 91)
  - Subjects Bo - C (Box 92)
  - Subjects D - G (Box 93)
  - Subjects H - L (Box 94)
  - Subjects Mc - O (Box 95)
  - Subjects P - R (Box 96)
  - Subjects S - U (Box 97)
  - Subjects V - Z and Indices (Box 98)
  - Subject Index and CW Times Index (Box 99)